Christina Chow

christinachow.me c3chow@gmail.com 818-486-9646 LinkedIn

About

A team player and quick learner who approaches every problem with a detail-oriented and analytical mindset.

Skills

UX/UI

Wireframing Prototyping Usability testing Design research User interviewing Design strategy Visual design

Tools

Github

Microsoft Office - Excel. PowerPoint, Access, Word Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Axure RP Sketch Invision HTML CSS POP Proto.io Balsamiq

Digital Advertising

Atlas MediaMind DoubleClick/DCM Comscore eMarketer Kantar STRATA/SBMS

Education

University of California, San Diego La Jolla, CA Bachelor of Arts -Economics June 2010

Designation Chicago, IL Major - UX March 2016 - August 2016

Work Experience

DESIGNATION - Product Manager (May 2016 - August 2016) Chicago, IL

- Designed mobile and web apps using the design thinking process in a highly immersive 70+ hours/week 18-week bootcamp
- Conducted user research and user testing, delivered wireframes, user flows and low and high fidelity prototypes to clients including:

Ezza Salon:

A local nail salon dedicated to helping streamline the nail salon experience for both users and owners from booking to completion of booked appointment.

Life Fluent:

A learning ESL chrome extension with the goal of exploring how teachers can best interact with students

Canvas Worldwide - Senior Digital Strategist, Shopping (December 2015 - May 2016)

Los Angeles, CA

- Ensured executions across Tier I and II campaigns met Kia Automotive's expectations by frequently collaborating with all parties including the creative agency, the internal teams within the agency, and the client
- Trained new team members on digital landscape, client best practices, and reviewed their deliverables before forwarding to upper management or client

Initiative - Senior Digital Strategist, Media Planner, Assistant Planner (March 2012 - December 2015)

Los Angeles, CA

- Strategically planned and executed three year-long digital media campaigns for Kia Automotive
- Developed and presented quarterly reviews with vendors to analyze KPI performance
- Researched unique opportunities and built recommendations for campaign optimizations
- Managed budget allocations and the day-to-day implementation of campaign activities to guarantee efficient and effective campaigns

ID Media - Assistant Account Executive

(February 2011 - March 2012)

Los Angeles, CA

- Assisted in the development of traditional media strategies and plans for Meineke and Time Warner
- Monitored day-to-day operations of client media activity in billing, insertion orders, and trafficking of all creative units
- Planned the accounts' activities in the following media channels: print, TV, radio, and out of home

Initiative - Freelance Assistant Media Planner

(December 2010) Los Angeles, CA

Nielsen Company/ Nielsen Claritas, Inc. - Research Analyst Intern (June 2009 - June 2010) La Jolla, CA